[Music]
welcome to another short episode of
what's cooking today we will be looking
at the ability to edit your purchase
document emails before sending
them so if we go to
purchase orders for
instance now if you click on print send
you'll find a new button just like you
find in the sales documents which is
sent by email
and if you click that button well you'll
get the familiar experience of the email
editor where you can edit the email in
whatever way you like add attachments
and so on and so forth before sending
them to your
supplier this Nifty little Edition was
built by a Community member through the
code development
initiative to beas locked the idea uh
that this would be a useful addition to
the product
and million decided to pick it up and
implemented this so that this now can
release with
2025 wave
1 thanks for watching